{
    "id": "d1cff28308d64361957439fa4fcc9229",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Our garden looks awful this summer. There are too ……………. weeds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "faefe96c5bac4666b8a3b4982647da2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ………………. flowering plants in our garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2caf0b18d054448986de07212b2977d"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………….. pages did you read?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6cc750cc56b435ca85f68810f287e43"
        },
        {
            "question": "They say …………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdf8e53190cd4bcf8f37d3f4bd095bd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am having ……………….. trouble passing my driving exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lot of",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c50ba67950524c109451ced5c18b886a"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... people can afford a home these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cc6783733b1405790002fcb39744331"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have ……………….. patience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13ac484dacfb4e3297ec3cdf67e5a288"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns ..................... money than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f894cc35f6a4215b85f28cb77906243"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... of the information proved to be outdated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbc0c93806ff4786ae4301ec32329cf0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t use ……………….. fertilizer last spring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8efd50ef6385432792afba493f2eb5a3"
        }
    ]
}